/*
 * ------------------------------------------------------------
 * IMPORTANT: The contents of this file are auto-generated.
 *
 * This file may be updated by the Shopify admin theme editor
 * or related systems. Please exercise caution as any changes
 * made to this file may be overwritten.
 * ------------------------------------------------------------
 */
{
  "sections": {
    "banner": {
      "type": "banner--page",
      "settings": {
        "layout": "default",
        "height": 150,
        "horizontalAlignment": "center",
        "verticalAlignment": "middle",
        "fontSize": "big",
        "contentColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "fillColor": "#c2a6ce",
        "overlayOpacity": 0,
        "overlayColor": "#000000"
      }
    },
    "content": {
      "type": "page",
      "settings": {
        "layout": "default",
        "enableShortcodes": false
      }
    },
    "27468bd0-302e-4f53-838c-7025b1fb8216": {
      "type": "section__faq",
      "blocks": {
        "de642591-471d-4d90-a612-ba3bf9ea224b": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>What are your shipping options?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>Crazy Gels offers standard and expedited shipping options. Standard shipping usually takes 5-15 business days, while expedited shipping delivers within 2-3 business days when available.</p>"
          }
        },
        "84b71835-d650-49bc-992c-3498d947566d": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>Do you ship internationally?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, we ship internationally to most countries. International shipping times may vary based on the destination and your shipping is FREE.</p>"
          }
        },
        "5dafd45a-3e28-4268-9039-63037e9c65b5": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>How can I track my order?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>Once your order is processed and shipped, you'll receive a confirmation email with a tracking number. You can use this number to track your package on our website or through the shipping carrierâ€™s website. </p><p>On very light or small  items no tracking will be added unless priority shipping is chosen.</p>"
          }
        },
        "2d9b28b5-7321-4ab6-9c1b-6c2c58cc1398": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>Are there any shipping fees?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>We offer free shipping on ALL Orders above 50</p><p> </p>"
          }
        },
        "ac980f17-de04-4525-a650-db2df6400573": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>Can I change my shipping address after placing an order?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>Unfortunately, we cannot change the shipping address once the order is placed. Please double-check your shipping information before completing your purchase.</p>"
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "de642591-471d-4d90-a612-ba3bf9ea224b",
        "84b71835-d650-49bc-992c-3498d947566d",
        "5dafd45a-3e28-4268-9039-63037e9c65b5",
        "2d9b28b5-7321-4ab6-9c1b-6c2c58cc1398",
        "ac980f17-de04-4525-a650-db2df6400573"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "custom_id": "",
        "displayFor": "display--both",
        "layout": "default",
        "nomargin": false,
        "scopedCSS": "",
        "height": 0,
        "padding": 0,
        "lineMargin": 12,
        "backgroundColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "backgroundPosition": "middle",
        "backgroundFilter": "none",
        "backdropIntensity": 50,
        "parallax": false,
        "backgroundPattern": false,
        "overlayOpacity": 0,
        "overlayColor": "#000000",
        "contentColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "horizontalAlignment": "center",
        "verticalAlignment": "middle",
        "maxContentWidth": 100,
        "heading": "Shipping FAQ",
        "headingColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "subheading": "",
        "subheadingColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "subheadingPosition": "above",
        "headingAlignment": "center",
        "textContent": ""
      }
    },
    "fde1513c-2dc5-4560-8380-6c831830dbd0": {
      "type": "section__faq",
      "blocks": {
        "c32be590-f52d-436e-88c6-e94209337d48": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>What is your return policy?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>Crazy Gels accepts returns within 30 days of purchase for a full refund or exchange. Items must be unused and in their original packaging.</p>"
          }
        },
        "e8007bfb-fe11-4b0d-add5-23c477d538ae": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>How do I initiate a return?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>To initiate a return, please contact our customer service team at [email or phone number] with your order number and reason for return. They will guide you through the process.</p>"
          }
        },
        "24819a27-94e0-4535-9b2f-fb2f5c341120": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>Are there any items that cannot be returned?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>For hygiene reasons, we cannot accept returns on opened or used or unused products : gels, oils, shampoos, conditioners, nail polishes, personal care or hygiene products unless they are damaged or defective and in original wrappings.</p>"
          }
        },
        "8bfc7ed1-8814-4391-bf41-5a50057d2b9f": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>Do I have to pay for return shipping?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>Customers are responsible for return shipping costs.</p>"
          }
        },
        "7b9de28f-f955-4502-9d3c-68becf03295a": {
          "type": "accordion",
          "settings": {
            "question": "<p><strong>How long does it take to process a refund?</strong></p>",
            "answer": "<p>Once we receive your returned item, we aim to process the refund within 5-7 business days. The refund will be issued to your original payment method.</p>"
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "c32be590-f52d-436e-88c6-e94209337d48",
        "e8007bfb-fe11-4b0d-add5-23c477d538ae",
        "24819a27-94e0-4535-9b2f-fb2f5c341120",
        "8bfc7ed1-8814-4391-bf41-5a50057d2b9f",
        "7b9de28f-f955-4502-9d3c-68becf03295a"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "custom_id": "",
        "displayFor": "display--both",
        "layout": "default",
        "nomargin": false,
        "scopedCSS": "",
        "height": 0,
        "padding": 0,
        "lineMargin": 12,
        "backgroundColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "backgroundPosition": "middle",
        "backgroundFilter": "none",
        "backdropIntensity": 50,
        "parallax": false,
        "backgroundPattern": false,
        "overlayOpacity": 0,
        "overlayColor": "#000000",
        "contentColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "horizontalAlignment": "center",
        "verticalAlignment": "middle",
        "maxContentWidth": 100,
        "heading": "Returns and Exchanges FAQ",
        "headingColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "subheading": "",
        "subheadingColor": "rgba(0,0,0,0)",
        "subheadingPosition": "above",
        "headingAlignment": "center",
        "textContent": ""
      }
    }
  },
  "order": [
    "banner",
    "content",
    "27468bd0-302e-4f53-838c-7025b1fb8216",
    "fde1513c-2dc5-4560-8380-6c831830dbd0"
  ]
}
